<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Android-app-2017</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="home_string">Home</string>
    <string name="events_string">Events</string>
    <string name="workshops_string">Workshops</string>
    <string name="summit_string">Summit</string>
    <string name="sponsors_string">Sponsors</string>
    <string name="aboutus_string">About Us</string>
    <string name="openDrawer">open</string>
    <string name="closeDrawer">close</string>
    <string name="intentExtra">target</string>
    <string name="title_activity_events">EventsActivity</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!-- Toolbar titles when navigation menu item is selected -->
    <string-array name="nav_item_activity_titles">
        <item>Home</item>
        <item>Events</item>
        <item>Workshops</item>
        <item>Summit</item>
        <item>Sponsors</item>
        <item>About Us</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="activity_title_about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="activity_title_privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="action_clear_all">Clear All</string>
    <string name="action_logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="action_mark_all_read">Mark All as Read</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_us">AboutUsActivity</string>

    <string name="shows_text">If you thought Freestyl Air were amazing and were left spellbound by Adelaida\'s performance then you are in for an experience of a life time. Elevate your New Year experience to get mesmerized by the shows from the future that break boundaries between imagination and reality at the captivating environs of IIT Madras! Witness artists from across the globe enthrall thousands in the audience with their \'tech-nique\' and \'tech-tics\' that will test your notions of the impossible. With \‘Augment\’ being the theme this year get ready to be awed by the huge spectrum of shows and exhibitions about to come your way this Shaastra! </string>
    <string name="envisage_text">Shaastra introduced a technologically aided cultural show 5 years ago - Envisage; which is one of its kind in India. Envisage is a technical marvel as the fusion of art and technology that pleasures your visual senses and overwhelms you with audio effects. Have you ever seen creating images and patterns out of flowing water? Have you ever seen music coming out of empty hands? Have you ever seen a guy dancing turns into amazing graphics? Envisage-5.0 brings you all of it. You are going to feel the pinnacle of entertainment with fascinating technology involved through our projects. It is going to be an exciting and exhilarating experience. Feast your eyes and ears on the enticing projects coming together as a show completely run by students of IIT Madras. After four successful editions of Envisage, this year Shaastra 2017 presents you Envisage-5.0 on Day 1, which is going to be more bigger and better.</string>
    <string name="exhibitions_text">Exhibitions showcases a plethora of innovations and recent developments in science and technology from all around the world. It\’s a platform for tech enthusiasts and students from all over the country to learn, experience and interact with experts who have brought these into existence.The theme of Shaastra this year is Augment - which focuses on assistive technologies for the differently abled, virtual and augmented reality, exoskeletons and wearables, among other such concepts which will help us unlock new dimensions. But cool innovations not falling under these verticals are most definitely welcome. Do you think your company has products like these which will enthrall the audience and capture their imaginations ? Do you want to reach out to students, scientists, potential customers and various other MNC\’s coming down to Shaastra every year ? Do you want to associate with brand IIT Madras, the best engineering college in the country ?</string>
</resources>
