<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Android-app-2017</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="home_string">Home</string>
    <string name="events_string">Events</string>
    <string name="workshops_string">Workshops</string>
    <string name="shows_string">Shows</string>
    <string name="summit_string">Summit</string>
    <string name="sponsors_string">Sponsors</string>
    <string name="aboutus_string">About Us</string>
    <string name="openDrawer">open</string>
    <string name="closeDrawer">close</string>
    <string name="intentExtra">target</string>
    <string name="title_activity_events">EventsActivity</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!-- Toolbar titles when navigation menu item is selected -->
    <string-array name="nav_item_activity_titles">
        <item>Home</item>
        <item>Events</item>
        <item>Workshops</item>
        <item>Shows</item>
        <item>Summit</item>
        <item>Sponsors</item>
        <item>About Us</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="activity_title_about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="activity_title_privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="action_clear_all">Clear All</string>
    <string name="action_logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="action_mark_all_read">Mark All as Read</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_us">AboutUsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_item_list">Items</string>
    <string name="title_item_detail">Item Detail</string>
    <string name="title_activity_vertical">VerticalActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_workshop_vertical">WorkshopVerticalActivity</string>

    <string name="shows_text">Coming Soon! Stay tuned for updates!</string>
    <string name="envisage_text">Shaastra introduced a technologically aided cultural show 5 years ago - Envisage; which is one of its kind in India. Envisage is a technical marvel as the fusion of art and technology that pleasures your visual senses and overwhelms you with audio effects. Have you ever seen creating images and patterns out of flowing water? Have you ever seen music coming out of empty hands? Have you ever seen a guy dancing turns into amazing graphics? Envisage-5.0 brings you all of it. You are going to feel the pinnacle of entertainment with fascinating technology involved through our projects. It is going to be an exciting and exhilarating experience. Feast your eyes and ears on the enticing projects coming together as a show completely run by students of IIT Madras. After four successful editions of Envisage, this year Shaastra 2017 presents you Envisage-5.0 on Day 1, which is going to be more bigger and better.</string>
    <string name="exhibitions_text">Coming Soon! Stay tuned for updates!</string>

    <string name="summit_main_para1">This year’s Summit strives to bring about a change in society by addressing an issue that is taken for granted by most people: <b>Accessibility.</b></string>
    <string name="summit_main_para2">Climbing stairs, listening to a lecture, reading a billboard, expressing dissent are some activities that most of us tend to perform quite effortlessly. Turning a “blind eye” to a “lame joke” is something that comes naturally to a lot of us. We crib to no end when people refuse to talk to us in a language we understand because it makes us feel like an outsider.</string>
    <string name="summit_main_para3">If there is one thing that human beings hate, it is the feeling of being excluded or pitied upon, as this is a constant reminder of what one cannot do.</string>
    <string name="summit_main_para4">Accessibility is an attempt to get rid of this exclusion in various important spheres – physical environments, public spaces, the digital realm, education, employment, technology, transport. It is concerned with the removal of barriers, to set the record straight on what causes a disability: not an individual’s inability to do something but the society’s tendency to throw unnecessary obstacles. Accessibility is a spectrum - it means usability, it means removing limitations and tapping opportunities.</string>
    <string name="summit_main_para5">The <b>International Accessibility Summit of Shaastra 2017</b>, IIT Madras, a 4 day-long event to be held between <b>31st December, 2016 to 3rd January, 2017</b>, is a platform for multiple stakeholders in the field of Accessibility and Assistive Technology to come together and share their knowledge. It is a chance for students from various fields of study to meet and ideate on how to make India truly accessible.</string>
</resources>
