<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Android-app-2017</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="home_string">Home</string>
    <string name="events_string">Events</string>
    <string name="workshops_string">Workshops</string>
    <string name="shows_string">Shows</string>
    <string name="summit_string">Summit</string>
    <string name="sponsors_string">Sponsors</string>
    <string name="aboutus_string">About Us</string>
    <string name="openDrawer">open</string>
    <string name="closeDrawer">close</string>
    <string name="intentExtra">target</string>
    <string name="title_activity_events">EventsActivity</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!-- Toolbar titles when navigation menu item is selected -->
    <string-array name="nav_item_activity_titles">
        <item>Home</item>
        <item>Events</item>
        <item>Workshops</item>
        <item>Shows</item>
        <item>Summit</item>
        <item>Sponsors</item>
        <item>About Us</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="activity_title_about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="activity_title_privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="action_clear_all">Clear All</string>
    <string name="action_logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="action_mark_all_read">Mark All as Read</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_us">AboutUsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_item_list">Items</string>
    <string name="title_item_detail">Item Detail</string>
    <string name="title_activity_vertical">VerticalActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_workshop_vertical">WorkshopVerticalActivity</string>

    <string name="shows_text">Coming Soon! Stay tuned for updates!</string>
    <string name="envisage_text">Shaastra introduced a technologically aided cultural show 5 years ago - Envisage; which is one of its kind in India. Envisage is a technical marvel as the fusion of art and technology that pleasures your visual senses and overwhelms you with audio effects. Have you ever seen creating images and patterns out of flowing water? Have you ever seen music coming out of empty hands? Have you ever seen a guy dancing turns into amazing graphics? Envisage-5.0 brings you all of it. You are going to feel the pinnacle of entertainment with fascinating technology involved through our projects. It is going to be an exciting and exhilarating experience. Feast your eyes and ears on the enticing projects coming together as a show completely run by students of IIT Madras. After four successful editions of Envisage, this year Shaastra 2017 presents you Envisage-5.0 on Day 1, which is going to be more bigger and better.</string>
    <string name="exhibitions_text">Coming Soon! Stay tuned for updates!</string>

    <string name="summit_main_para1">This year’s Summit strives to bring about a change in society by addressing an issue that is taken for granted by most people: <b>Accessibility.</b></string>
    <string name="summit_main_para2">Climbing stairs, listening to a lecture, reading a billboard, expressing dissent are some activities that most of us tend to perform quite effortlessly. Turning a “blind eye” to a “lame joke” is something that comes naturally to a lot of us. We crib to no end when people refuse to talk to us in a language we understand because it makes us feel like an outsider.</string>
    <string name="summit_main_para3">If there is one thing that human beings hate, it is the feeling of being excluded or pitied upon, as this is a constant reminder of what one cannot do.</string>
    <string name="summit_main_para4">Accessibility is an attempt to get rid of this exclusion in various important spheres – physical environments, public spaces, the digital realm, education, employment, technology, transport. It is concerned with the removal of barriers, to set the record straight on what causes a disability: not an individual’s inability to do something but the society’s tendency to throw unnecessary obstacles. Accessibility is a spectrum - it means usability, it means removing limitations and tapping opportunities.</string>
    <string name="summit_main_para5">The <b>International Accessibility Summit of Shaastra 2017</b>, IIT Madras, a 4 day-long event to be held between <b>31st December, 2016 to 3rd January, 2017</b>, is a platform for multiple stakeholders in the field of Accessibility and Assistive Technology to come together and share their knowledge. It is a chance for students from various fields of study to meet and ideate on how to make India truly accessible.</string>
    <string name="summit_events_para1"><b>Case Study Competition:</b> The Case Study Competition aims to bring to focus the obstacles with regard to Accessibility in India. Participants will get the opportunity to work on problem statements provided by professional organizations tailored from real-life challenges. They will be required to work in groups with students from different backgrounds. The objective is to analyze the problem, discuss existent models, and present a workable solution.</string>
    <string name="summit_events_para2"><b>Social Enterprise Competition:</b> This event is targeted towards students interested in entrepreneurship in the social sector.It will be a chance for innovative individuals to devise a profitable and practical business model intended to improve accessibility in terms of technology, service delivery, legal aid etc., and find methods to implement it. </string>
    <string name="summit_events_para3"><b>Hackathon for the Visually Impaired:</b> This is a platform for visually impaired students to demonstrate their proficiency in computer science and programming. It aims to bring to focus the immense potential for employability and independence that people with disabilities have but is often ignored. To bring out the best in the participants,International Accessibility Summit has collaborated with Vision-Aid to teach visually impaired students the basics of programming. For this, students from IIT Madras have volunteered to act as teaching assistants.</string>
    <string name="summit_events_para4"><b>Central Panel Discussion:</b> The Summit will host a panel comprised of experts working in different ways to make the country more accessible. The panelists are from varied fields - policy making, assistive technology, corporate social responsibility, and the social sector. The discussion will bring to light the world standards for inclusivity and how India can match up to them.</string>
    <string name="summit_events_para5"><b>Lectures and Workshops:</b> Participants will be exposed to different aspects of the theme of Accessibility through lectures covering topics of policy development and assistive technology. The participants will also take part in a Sensitization workshop to break the social stigma against disability and provide an in-depth understanding of the topic of inclusion and accessibility.They will also take part in a Web Accessibility workshop to understand accessibility of Information technology.</string>
    <string name="summit_speakers_para1"><b>Suranga Nanayakkara</b> is an Assistant Professor from the Engineering Product Development Pillar at Singapore University of Technology and Design (SUTD). Before joining SUTD, Suranga was a Postdoctoral Associate at the Fluid Interfaces group, MIT Media Lab. In 2011, he founded the "Augmented Human Lab" to explore ways of creating ‘enabling’ human-computer interfaces as natural extensions of our body, mind and behaviour. Suranga is among that rare breed of engineers that has a sense of “humanity” in technology. This ranges from practical behavioral issues, understanding real-life contexts in which technologies function, and understanding where technologies can be not just exciting or novel, but have a meaningful impact on the way people live. For the totality and breadth of achievements, he has won many awards including been recognized as a young inventor under 35 (TR35 award) in the Asia Pacific region by MIT TechReview, Outstanding Young Persons of Sri Lanka (TOYP), and INK Fellow. His work is most important to the people whose lives it most directly impacts: those who face challenged to function in the world due to sensory deficits in hearing or vision.</string>
    <string name="summit_speakers_para2"><b>Amba Salelkar</b> is a lawyer who specializes in law and policy research focused on the inclusion of persons with disabilities. In 2012, she joined the Inclusive Planet Centre for Disability Law and Policy, Chennai, where she began work on advocating for legal harmonization with the UN Convention on the Rights of Persons with Disabilities. In 2014, she was awarded the Chevening Gurukul Fellowship Programme for Leadership and Excellence. She now works with the Equals Centre for Promotion of Social Justice, an organization that focuses on effective law and policy interventions towards the inclusion of persons with disabilities with a focus on stakeholder participation, which was founded in 2014, and is based in Chennai.</string>
    <string name="summit_speakers_para3"><b>George Abraham</b>, an Ashoka Fellow since 2001, is a social Entrepreneur, inspirational speaker and a master communicator. After completing his post-graduate in Operations Research and graduating in Mathematics from St Stephen’s College, University of Delhi between 1976-81, he worked in Advertising and Sales Promotion at Ogilvy Benson and Mather between 1982-89. He is the Founding Chairman of WBCC (World Blind Cricket Council), who pioneered and organized the first ever World Cup of cricket for the blind at New Delhi 1998, which led him to launch competitive blind cricket in India 1990. He has also co-authored a book on Inclusive Education which was published by Sage Publications. His entrepreneurship journey started when he launched Project Eyeway, a single stop knowledge resource on life with blindness which aimed at bringing together information as well as organisations working with the blind onto a single platform. He was also accredited of conceiving and producing the 13 part TV serial Nazar Ya Nazariya. He has been a recipient of several awards such as Limca Book of Records People of the year 2007, CF Andrews Distinguished Alumni Award (St Stephen’s College) in 2015 and the Sanskriti Award in 1994. He has also had the honour of being the Olympic Torch Relay runner in 1996, being part of Discovery People series on Discovery Channel in 1998 and being a part of Aviva Forward Thinkers Campaign in 2008. He has also given a TedX Talk in 2012 at Bangalore.</string>
    <string name="summit_speakers_para4"><b>Dipendra Manocha</b> is the lead of training and technical support at DAISY Consortium. He is the president of the DAISY Forum of India, a network of more than 130 organisations in India serving persons with blindness and low vision, and National Association for the Blind (Delhi branch). An Ashoka fellow (2005) and a Natinal Award winner (2007), he has managed or coordinated several technological development or implementation projects. Some of these include Development of Braille transcriptions and screen reading softwares in Indian languages, Accessible content creation projects and establishment of digital library for persons with blindness, and ICT literacy for persons with blindness and application of technology for work place solution for opening new venues of employment and education for persons with blindness. He worked as a consultant for Delhi University for establishing a resource centre for persons with disability, and as a resource person in a series of workshops on accessible built environment conducted by the Chief Commissioner Disabilities, Govt. of India.</string>
</resources>
